Zonta Club of Albany; Records apap399
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1939-2019; 3; 2.4 cubic ft.
  - Zontian Program Issue, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)